who was it that said if you think you
understand quantum physics you don't
understand quantum physics consciousness
intelligence freewill determinism black
holes protecting the planet from
asteroids traps nuclear magnetic
resonance superconductors photons
special intelligence machine learning
classical physics thing I can tell us
them to get very hot as I start speaking
so tell me if I start to look really
shiny quantum physics puts everything
into question it defies every intuition
you have about the natural world quantum
is a very strange regime of physics
things can exist in this state of
superposition where they can be like
ghosting on each other where they could
be this and that at the same time be
entanglement quantum entanglement to
objects if that quantum mechanically
entangled I still strongly related to
each other even though they can be a
vast distance apart there's a notion of
the multiverse there's a whole family of
hardwoods and different states and going
through different experiences and
different life trajectories the famous
one is quantum tunneling tunneling
tunneling tunneling is the slippage
between universes for a long time people
thought those effects only existed in
the microscopic domain like atoms
electrons photons but really it's the
theory of our universe so if you want to
build a quantum computer you want to
incorporate those new phenomenon into
information processing maybe in quantum
computation is one of those instruments
that's going to allow us to see quantum
effects at the human scale Google and
NASA have teamed up to share one of the
world's first commercial quantum
computers this machine made by Canada's
d-wave will be installed in a NASA
Research Center in California this is
the inside of one of our dilution
refrigerators all of this infrastructure
is to basically operate the chip at a
temperature that Stuart is a magnitude
colder than interstellar space
[Music]
the the processor is a quantum computer
but users things called qubits
everyone's being either one for a zero
qubit can also be both at the same time
therefore bringing about a quantum leap
in terms of power
harnessing principles of reality that
are up until very recently completely
not reservable by us is just fascinating
in ways that i can't completely
articulate the overwhelmingly obvious
killer app for quantum computation is
optimization optimization problems are
extremely difficult problems actually
all Google service centers together will
not be capable of coming up with the
best solution to these optimization
problems as they get larger so now what
is an optimization problem I give you an
example you want to do a trip through
South America and you want to visit a
number of cities and then you ask what
is the cheapest ticket I can get to
visit let's say 20 cities and you can of
course different routes and different
airlines and sort of imagine I list all
the different options I have for my
different routes to travel to the cities
we currently have civilization we
generate vast amounts of data it could
be climate data genomic data but it's
very difficult to generate useful
insights off times from that data if you
can solve optimization problems better
you have an important resource at your
hand
[Music]
I think unless it teaches us that we
should be naive about the world that we
shouldn't think about the world as a
simple machine since forces us to
consider you know more sophisticated
notions of how the reality around us is
actually shape I can't ask it how long
I'll live or the meaning of life really
we don't know what the best questions
are to ask that computer that's exactly
what we're trying to understand now to
me the most important question is are we
alone and I have a feeling that quantum
computers as they mature are going to
help us answer that question this is
have caused a more long-term research
endeavor and they're still tremendous
obstacles and and big questions some of
those will be addressed in d-wave some
will be addressed at NASA in some at
Google I wasn't sure I would be able to
experiment with a quantum computational
device in my lifetime and now I'm
confident that I will be able to how
amazing it is that we with our monkey
heritage monkey brains and monkey
fingers have somehow lucked into a brain
that allows us to ask legitimate
questions about the nature of physical
reality
that's so cool
with that human risk to go forth into
the unknown frontier
whether it's space exploration or
quantum exploration we do it because we
must we do it because that's what it
means to be human
[Music]