my name is Sonia and I am the second
presenter October 10th
I believe you're smart intelligence and
listening skills so I believe you
understand she explanation about basic
background about our from now I'm going
to show the structure of green single
continent entities from sapphire zero
zero zero one orientation we call that C
phase of 2h the other news soft three of
these devices and after that I try
bomber layer is grown a low temperature
maybe it's about 550 Celsius as you can
see this devices there are many layers
each layer has ocean of helping
transportation with carriers and
enhancing quantum efficiencies but the
most important part in these devices is
this Activision active region forms
single quantum structure consisting of
internal nitrile to an off stronger
later
zebb achieved by and timing tomorrow
night right and we type a reverb and
track from each electrode injected
carriers moved into where later and by
electrical cooler horses they create
acetone and we call this phenomenon a
combination
infantry combination happens light is
being emitted from this where there and
another thing about this continent right
over there
it has functional reduce the interface
trapped between I have not try and
I saw straight now you are watching your
intensity as a function of wavelength it
is divided into three different colors
if it knew more fraction increases the
energy gap is getting smaller it causes
the reduction of wavelengths what does
that mean
that means you can change and rediscover
through changing into fractions while
making devices and here's the second
thing you need in the experimental big
wavelengths on green LED is about 525
millimeters but for references other
officers condition Nick wavelengths or
Breen is about 419 others it's a little
bit longer because of this band gap in
general we can explain this band gap
narrowing into two different reasons the
first one is different from expansion
coefficient second one is large lattice
mismatch now you are watching The Fool
with with have maximum on PL spectra as
a function of big wavelengths even
become that wavelength increases the
value of a fluid will have maximum also
increases here is the mechanism of this
if you increase into mole fraction it
causes reducing of energy so it
increases inferences between where there
and very earlier so it is caused by the
mismatch of the lattice and the thermal
expansion
between well and very layers here's the
output power is a function of award
current our team wrote it down each
output power and external quantum
efficiency here is to two important
thing you don't have to remember the
first one is saturation above 16 in the
out there the output power almost
saturated but probably due to the
generation of it the second thing you
have to remember it is comparison
between losing quantum LEDs green and
yellow
this blue single quantum and LEDs has
much higher output power rather than
green and yellow this reason can be
explained by this two reasons first one
is differences between the well and the
most thermal expansion coefficient the
second one is integrated nitride has
large lattice mismatch this is the last
figure of our presentations it's about
upper power is a function of a peak
wavelength if you increase peak
wavelengths the output power decreases
it's due to the large strain between
well and
laters now let's compare with newly
developed diode engine light rising the
quantum enemies and the conventional
ones in phosphide and as you can see the
output power the engine on my tricycle
ultimately it has much higher output
power rather than its to one so you can
see more bright color and as you can see
the peak wavelength we pointed out five
hundred and twenty-five millimeters dead
525 represents the brewery color of each
wavelength but I'm under the 55 at five
hundred and seventy is not purely green
it's like yellowish green so in its
final analysis if you want to see more
bright and what a green LEDs why don't
you use this is the conclusion of our
presentations
the first one is high brightness
innovative night rising responsibilities
were brought by the technology culture
this we can see quantum well structure
and number two and number three is just
experimental data and comparison all
this and number four it's about
fabrication fabrication of practical
visible LEDs in the range from blue to
yellow is possible using three to five I
tried materials that means we could
change LEDs color through changing into
mole fractions so you can see blue to
yellow color this is our references this
is the end of our presentations if you
have any questions our team will
answer to you as much as we though